

Prague, Czech Republic



lukas.bunat@gmail.com



+420 731 277 533



bunatl



lukasbunat



Lukáš **Buňát**



ASS

Software & Full-Stack Developer and Data Engineer

I have been in IT and specifically in software development for 4+ years. When I was using C++ and JAVA often speed, efficiency and design patterns were top priorities. In last two years, I transitioned into web development and finally, last year I found a passion for Full-Stack development. My focus is to build platforms that help grow and scale company projects.

I don't just code, thanks to my strong educational background, I have a wide range of theoretical informatics, computer architecture structuring and planning skills that helps me finding clever solutions. I have had studied at many different universities all over the world and I take great pride in my international education. I thrive on multicultural teams and enjoy resolving everyday challenges. I am always open to new opportunities and eager to learn more!



Technical Skills

Software development

Full-Stack technologies

Software Collaboration Theoretical informatics Computer architecture

Other

C, C++, JAVA SE, bash, AHK

Front End	React.js 16.8, JavaScript ES6/2017, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, SA
Back End	Node.js, express.js, JAVA EE
Database	SQL (MySQL, MS SQL Server), No-SQL (MongoDB, Mongoose)

Tableau, Rapid Miner, Wolfram Alpha, Modelio, MS Office Suite, AutoCAD, Inventor

GIT, JIRA, Trello, Slack

Calculus, Linear Algebra, Algorithms, Speed and memory efficiency

Data and number representation, OS/memory/cache/FS management, multitasking

Business Intelligence, UML, Testing

Data analysis, Logical thinking, Critical & analytical thinking



Experiences

Work Experiences

Freelancer, "on and off" contracts 09/2019 - Present

Business websites

(C) GitHub

- Web application (MERN)
- Full-Stack (JS, node.js, react), Wordpress

Network Infrastructure Specialist 05/2018–05/2019

O2 Czech Republic a.s., Prague, Czech Republic

- O2TV platform and company internal applications software development
- https://www.o2tv.cz/, O2TV
- C, Java EE, JS, HTML5, CSS3

Internships

Big Data Architect Trainee 10/2017–12/2017

Comillas Pontifical University, Madrid, Spain

- Application of Clustering Methods for Discovering Patterns of Energy
- PySpark, Jupyter, Hadoop

Network Engineer Trainee 03/2017-06/2017

Kyungpook National University, Daegu, South Korea

- Network routing and latency simulations on COOJA Simulator
- Wireshark, COOJA

From 2014 to 2019 I had been working as a tutor at international student club at Czech Technical University.



Soft Skills



New creative and innovative approaches to problem solving



Very good (cross-culture) communication for constructive teamwork



Enthusiastic about learning new things and technologies



Quick decisiveness, good decision-making (even uder pressure), leadership



Effective time managment to ensure tasks' deadlines are met



Education

University, Year(s) of Study		Field of study, Faculty	Location
y LA FROM	University of Economics	Information systems and technologies	Prague,
PRAZE	2019 - Present	Faculty of informatics and statistics	V Czech Republic
15.08	Czech Technical University	Open Informatics	Prague, Czech Republic
	2019	Faculty of Electrical Engineering	
(SFS)	University of Finance and Administration	Applied Informatics, Graduate, Bc.	Prague,
	2018-2019	Faculty of Economics	Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University	Information Systems and Management	Prague,
	2014–2018	Faculty of Information Technology	Czech Republic
THE REPORT OF THE PARTY OF THE	Kyungpook National University	Exchange studies	Daegu,
	2017	College of IT Engineering	South Korea
STEOF HOUSE	Indian Institute of Technology Madras	Exchange studies	Chennai,
Egg. Wander and S. S. S.	2016	Department of Computer Science	▼ India
TO CCCCC	Delft University of Technology	Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland	O Delft,
	2016	The ATHENS Programme	Netherlands
虚	Mayflower College of English	Summer language school	Plymouth,
	2012		V United Kingdom



Certificates



CISCO Academy

CCNA 1 (2013)



Autodesk AutoCAD (2014) Inventor (2014)



KFN of UNESCO

Cross Culture Awereness Programme